/**
 * @type {{
 *  question: string,
 *  answers: [ string, string ] | [ string, string, string ] | [ string, string, string, string ],
 *  correct: number,
 *  time: number
 * }[] }
 */
export const questions = [
    {
        question: "Which one is used for cutting Text",
        answers: [
            "Scissors",
            "Ctrl+Shift+V",
            "Ctrl+V",
            "Ctrl+X"
        ],
        correct: 3,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How many People have Alzheimer's?",
        answers: [
            "17,309,300",
            "6,712,478",
            "1,234,567",
            "I forget how many"
        ],
        correct: 1,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Which one is the Colon?",
        answers: [
            ";",
            "*",
            ":",
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How many toes does an Elephant have?",
        answers: [
            "5",
            "4",
            "3",
            "6"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Which one is used for Pasting Text?",
        answers: [
            "Ctrl+C",
            "Ctrl+Alt+V",
            "Ctrl+V",
            "Ctrl+X"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Which Hotkey is used for copying?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+C",
        "Ctrl+Shift+V",
        "Ctrl+V",
        "Ctrl+X"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "which hotkey is used for a Hyperlink?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+K",
        "Ctrl+Alt+L",
        "Ctrl+L",
        "Ctrl+W"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "Which Hotkey is used for Closing a tab?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+K",
        "Ctrl+FN+L",
        "Ctrl+L",
        "Ctrl+W"
        ],
        correct: 3,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How do you make a left indent?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+K",
        "Ctrl+Alt+L",
        "Ctrl+T",
        "Ctrl+W"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How do you save something?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+J",
        "Ctrl+Alt+I",
        "Ctrl+E",
        "Ctrl+S"
        ],
        correct: 3,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How do you Center a document?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+J",
        "Ctrl+CMD+I",
        "Ctrl+E",
        "Ctrl+S"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How do you Justify a document",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+J",
        "Ctrl+Alt+I",
        "Ctrl+E",
        "Ctrl+S"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "How do you make a hanging indent?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+M",
        "Ctrl+D",
        "Ctrl+U",
        "Ctrl+Q"
        ],
        correct: 3,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What is the hotkey for adding space after a paragraph?",
        answers: [
        "Ctrl+K",
        "Ctrl+FN+L",
        "Ctrl+T",
        "Ctrl+W"
        ],
        correct: 0,
        time: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What's your favorite color of the Alphabet?",
        answers: [
        "True",
        "False",
        "All of the above"
        ],
        correct: 2,
        time: 20
    }
]
 
